Unit 2 L-Ambjent Complex B, Telgent, Xemxija Hill, Xemxija, St Paul's Bay, SPB 9021, Malta

+356 7934 2920 | robvibart@gmail.com

https://www.linkedin.com/in/robert-vibart-78418071



OVERVIEW

Robert is a multi-skilled Graphics designer and Web designer with 13 years' experience designing a wide variety of designs, he has worked with various marketing personnel to concept, research and design campaigns for promotional print Ad-hoc, corporate collateral, and digital designs. The following are but a few of the companies that he has worked alongside – First National Bank, Investec Bank & ABSA Bank.

SKILLS

Project Management, Operations Manager, Diagnosis (Digital output)

Design software: Adobe CC 2021 Suite - Illustrator, InDesign, Photoshop, Premiere Pro, Flash(CS6), Maya Version 2018, Sketch Up 2019

Web Design - Visual Studio Code(IDE), HTML5, CSS, SASS, CSS Grid, Flexbox, GitHub, Figma, UI, Netlify.app (Static page development), Vectary 3D (Web platform), WordPress, MONO web builder, Google Analytics (basic experience)
Google Tag manager (basic experience), Banner snack (Social media Web App)

Microsoft Word, Microsoft Power Point, Microsoft Excel

EMPLOYMENT

Jet line Print on Demand 2009 - 2011

Production assistant and desktop publisher

- Worked with clients to conceptualize various Graphic design requirements for print
- Setting artwork for lithographic print output
- Setting artwork design for digital print output
- Setting large format designs for print output
- Logo design and concept creation
- Setting print for various finishing output
 - Foiling
 - Die cutting
 - Embossing

Studio-CX Design Studio

2011- 2012

Assistant Junior Graphic designer

- Assistant to senior Graphic designer.
- Assisted with design and development of layouts for financial reports for print digital output.
- Assisted team with typesetting and layout (CAPS) curriculum educational manuals for digital output.
- Redrew various images for vector output.
- Type setting redrawing statistical graphs for Barometer financial reports for the (Development Bank South Africa) DBSA.
- Created various logos for the company and its clients.

Cube Zoo Design Studio

2012- 2012(One month Internship)

Junior Graphic designer

- Assisted with design and development of web format animated banners (Adobe Flash CS6).
- Assisted with design and development of various logos for various clients.
- Designed and developed magazine layouts and typesetting both for digital output and print output.
- Assisted with coding static HTML and CSS websites using basic GitHub integration.
- Assisted team on 3D animation project 5min animation of their company mascot

Digital Color Bar 2012 - 2019

H.O.D of Graphic and Visual Communications Dept.

- Managed and ran multiple Graphic design concepts for print output.
- Oversee print production team duties and client requests.
- Managing production time frames and digital output requests.
- Maintained company job tracking system.
- Maintained company in-house Graphic design concepts and final print output.
- Assisted marketing personnel with conceptualization and campaign development.
- Managed and communicated with various print suppliers and production managers on digital job final output.
- Designed and developed eventing print collateral for First National Bank, Rand Merchant Bank and Investec Bank using corporate CI guides

Yellow Pages UAE, Malta

Web Designer, Social media designer

2020 - 2021

- Brief 45mins meeting over Google Meet with clients interested in Yellows Website platform
- Using online Web editor MONO to build and maintain Yellow's clients existing and current websites
- Working with team to implement good UI and UX practices on website designs
- Working with both H.O.D of Marketing and Digital Marketing Executive to design animated Social media designs
- Working with Sales team while working on websites to maintain and communicate production deadlines
- Using Banner snack, Illustrator, or Photoshop to build and design Social media designs with end user in mind

EDUCATION

Tertiary Education Willow ridge High

1998 - 2002(Matriculated)

Depth Animation Studios (Internship)

2002 - 2004

- Basic 3D Animation theory
- Junior Level (Maya Software)
 - o 3D Modelling
 - o 3D Lighting and Texturing
 - o 3D Computer Arts
 - Storyboard development

Boston Media house 2005 - 2007

- Graphic design (Diploma)
- Public relations
- Communication science
- Advertising
- Marketing

Boston Media house 2007 - 2009

- 3D Animation 3D Design (Diploma)
 - o Pixilation / Stop motion animation
 - o Illustration and 2D conceptualization 2D Animation
 - Storyboard and concept development

REFERENCES

Available upon request